{"data":[{"question":"The examiner must have pleased ________ my performance.","a":"for","b":"with","c":"about","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Please with sbd\/sth: be happy or satisfied with\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"They informed me about it. That's the ________ I received.","a":"inform","b":"informs","c":"informations","d":"information","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The + Noun \n- Information: uncountable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"She said she ________ this race.","a":"wants to win","b":"want to win","c":"wanted to win","d":"wanting to win","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original. \n+ If simple present, present perfect or the future is used in the reporting verb (i.e. says) the tense is retained.\u00a0\n+ If reporting a general truth the present tense will be retained or even the future tense can be used.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The thief was ________ to six months' imprisonment.","a":"given","b":"allowed","c":"sent","d":"sentenced","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sentence: if a judge sentences someone who is guilty of a crime, they give them a punishment.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Some people think that the camel ________ water in its hump.","a":"store","b":"stores","c":"stored","d":"had stored","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in simple present tense, if the subordinate clause the which shows an action occurring at the same time will be simple present tense \n- Subject ( the camel) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Instead of ________ about the good news, Tom seemed to be indifferent.","a":"exciting","b":"being excited","c":"to excite","d":"to be excited","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Instead of sth\/doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Women ________ to live longer than men.","a":"tend","b":"tendency","c":"tendentious","d":"tendentiously","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"I finally finished ________ at 7.00 p.m. and served dinner.","a":"cooking","b":"being cooked","c":"to cook","d":"to be cooked","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Finish doing sth","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you mind not ________ the radio until I have finished with this phone call?","a":"turning on","b":"being turned on","c":"to turn on","d":"to be turned on","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Would + S + Mind + Verb_ing: used for asking politely for something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"According to the third law of thermodynamics, _____ possible is 273.16 degrees centigrade.","a":"that temperature is lowest","b":"the temperature is lower","c":"lowest temperature","d":"the lowest temperature.","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the superlative form of short adjective (low)\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}